Elihu Thomson Papers 1865-1944 Mss.Ms.Coll.74
American Philosophical Society
- Series I. Professional Correspondence, Ca. 1870-1937; 52 boxes; 26 linear feet
  - Stockly, George W., 1894; 1 item (Box Series I-45)
  - Stockwell, Richard, n.d.; 1 item (Box Series I-45)
  - Stodola, A., 1910; 1 item (Box Series I-45)
  - Stone, C. W., 1917-1922; 4 items (Box Series I-45)
  - Stone & Downer Company, 1911; 1 item (Box Series I-45)
  - Stone, Harry E., 1928; 2 items (Box Series I-45)
    West Virginia University
  - Stone, Orra L., 1928; 2 items (Box Series I-45)
  - Stone & Webster, 1906-1930; 9 items (Box Series I-45)
  - Stott, Henry G., 1906-1914; 16 items (Box Series I-45)
    See also: A. I. E. E.
  - Stratford Company, 1924-1930; 4 items (Box Series I-46)
  - Stratton, S. W., 1901-1907; 21 items (Box Series I-46)
    See also: U. S. Gov. Treasury Dept. & Dept. of Commerce & Labor. A. I. E. E.
  - Stratton, S. W., 1908-1928; 26 items (Box Series I-46)
    See also: U. S. Gov. Dept. of Commerce & Labor
  - Street Railway Gazette, 1894; 1 item (Box Series I-46)
  - Street Railway Journal, 1892-1900; 4 items (Box Series I-46)
  - Street Railway Review, 1891-1899; 3 items (Box Series I-46)
    H. H. Windsor
  - Strobel, Charles, Jr., 1933; 1 item (Box Series I-46)
  - Strong, F. F., 1906; 1 item (Box Series I-46)
  - Structural Engineer, n.d.; 2 items (Box Series I-46)
  - Stuart, Emiley, n.d.; 1 item (Box Series I-46)
  - Stuart, George, 1886-1896; 5 items (Box Series I-46)
  - Stuart, Otis K., 1897-1898; 3 items (Box Series I-46)
  - Stuart, W. W., 1892; 1 item (Box Series I-46)
  - Sturtevant, L. H., 1909; 1 item (Box Series I-46)
  - Sullivan Brothers, 1892; 1 item (Box Series I-46)
    M. O. Sullivan
  - Sullivan, Eva T., 1931-1939; 16 items (Box Series I-46)
    Secretary to Elihu Thomson
  - Sullivan, Thomas F., 1933; 1 item (Box Series I-46)
  - Sun, 1900; 2 items (Box Series I-46)
  - Sunday Creek Coal Company, 1899; 1 item (Box Series I-46)
  - Sunny, B. E., 1897-1930; 18 items (Box Series I-46)
  - Sussdorf, Zaldo & Company, 1912; 4 items (Box Series I-46)
    Mr. Labrit & Mr. E. Zaldo
  - Sussfeld,Lorsch and Company, 1904-1919; 2 items (Box Series I-46)
  - Swain, George F., 1908-1913; 3 items (Box Series I-46)
    M. I. T. Dept. of Civil Engineering
  - Swampscott Historical Society. Board of Governors, 1921; 1 item (Box Series I-46)
  - Swampscott Land Trust, 1888; 2 items (Box Series I-46)
  - Swampscott Police Department, 1902; 1 item (Box Series I-46)
  - Swampscott Public Library, 1907-1934; 3 items (Box Series I-46)
  - Swan, Alfred, 1892-1916; 2 items (Box Series I-46)
  - Swasey, Ambrose, 1912-1937; 22 items (Box Series I-46)
  - Swasey, Raymond & Page, 1902; 1 item (Box Series I-46)
  - Sweetser, Moses, 1902; 2 items (Box Series I-46)
  - [Swinburne, James], 1891; 1 item (Box Series I-46)
  - Swope, Gerard, 1922-1935; 21 items (Box Series I-46)
  - System. The Magazine of Business, 1914-1923; 3 items (Box Series I-46)
  - " T ", 1909; 1 item (Box Series I-46)
  - Tagliabue, C. J. Manufacturing Company, 1930; 3 items (Box Series I-46)
  - Taitt, Francis M., 1905; 1 item (Box Series I-46)
  - Tatum, Edward S., 1891 (Box Series I-46)
  - Tavern Club, n.d.; 1 item (Box Series I-46)
  - Taylor, John B., 1911-1922; 5 items (Box Series I-46)
  - Taylor, J. M., 1910; 1 item (Box Series I-46)
  - Taylor, Robert S., 1892; 1 item (Box Series I-46)
  - Taylor & White, 1931; 1 item (Box Series I-46)
  - Tech Club of New Hampshire, 1921; 1 item (Box Series I-46)
  - Tech Show- 1918 & 1922, 2 items (Box Series I-46)
  - Technical Review, 1920; 1 item (Box Series I-46)
  - Technical World Magazine, 1906; 2 items (Box Series I-46)
  - Technology Christian Association, 1916; 1 item (Box Series I-46)
    A. G. Cushman
  - Technology Club, 1897-1921; 3 items (Box Series I-46)
  - Tedesco Country Club, 1904-1930; 5 items (Box Series I-46)
  - Tehuantepec Rubber Culture Company, 1901-1905; 3 items (Box Series I-46)
  - Telepost, 1908; 2 items (Box Series I-46)
  - Tel-U-Where Company of America, n.d.; 1 item (Box Series I-46)
  - Templeton Inn, 1925; 1 item (Box Series I-46)
  - Tenney, A. B., 1911; 1 item (Box Series I-46)
  - Teraoka, Captain, 1920; 1 item (Box Series I-46)
  - Terry, Charles A., 1902; 2 items (Box Series I-46)
  - Terry, Charles W., 1928; 3 items (Box Series I-46)
    Electric Storage Battery Co.
  - Teterle, Fred, 1930; 1 item (Box Series I-46)
  - Texas Company, 1933; 1 item (Box Series I-46)
  - Textile Club, 1892-1905; 3 items (Box Series I-46)
  - Thayer, W. S., 1924; 4 items (Box Series I-47)
    See also: Harvard Univ.
  - Thermal Syndicate, Ltd., 1916; 1 item (Box Series I-47)
  - Thibault, L. D., 1893; 1 item (Box Series I-47)
  - Third Pan American Scientific Congress, 1924; 2 items (Box Series I-47)
    Organization Committee
  - Thomas, B F., 1897; 1 item (Box Series I-47)
    Ohio State Univ. Physical Lab.
  - Thompson & Company, Inc., 1932; 1 item (Box Series I-47)
  - Thompson, Homer, n.d.; 1 item (Box Series I-47)
  - Thompson, J. Webber, 1891; 1 item (Box Series I-47)
  - Thompson, Jane S., 1916; 1 item (Box Series I-47)
  - Thompson, John, 1909; 1 item (Box Series I-47)
  - Thompson, L. P., 1906; 1 item (Box Series I-47)
  - Thompson, P. P., 1892; 1 item (Box Series I-47)
  - Thompson, Silvanus P., 1884-1914; 12 items (Box Series I-47)
  - Thompson, Ted R., 1929; 1 item (Box Series I-47)
  - Thompson, Tenney & Crawford, 1902; 1 item (Box Series I-47)
  - Thomson, Clarissa Hovey, 1904-1931; 20 items (Box Series I-47)
  - Thomson, Clarissa Hovey, Aug.- Sept. 1933; 25 items (Box Series I-47)
  - Thomson, Clarissa Hovey, Oct.- Dec. 1933; 17 items (Box Series I-47)
  - Thomson, Clarissa Hovey, 1934; 31 items (Box Series I-47)
  - Thomson, Clarissa Hovey, 1935; 24 items (Box Series I-47)
  - Thomson, Clarissa Hovey, 1936; 9 items (Box Series I-47)
  - Thomson, Clarissa Hovey, Jan.- May 1937; 35 items (Box Series I-47)
  - Thomson, Clarissa Hovey, Jun.-Oct. 1937; 32 items (Box Series I-47)
  - Thomson, Clarissa Hovey, Nov.-Dec. 1937; 59 items (Box Series I-47)
  - Thomson, Clarissa Hovey, 1938; 43 items (Box Series I-47)
  - Thomson, Clarissa Hovey, 1939; 38 items (Box Series I-47)
  - Thomson, D. (Brother), 1892; 1 item (Box Series I-47)
    Hamilton Elec. Light and Power Co.
  - Thomson-Houston Carbon Company, 1891; 1 item (Box Series I-47)
  - Thomson-Houston Electric Company, 1891-1936; 6 items (Box Series I-47)
  - Thomson, J. Arthur, 1922; 2 items (Box Series I-47)
  - Thomson, Malcolm, 1927; 1 item (Box Series I-47)
  - Thomson, Martha, Otis and Fred (Siblings), 1894-1933 (Box Series I-47)
  - Thomson Quarter Century Club, 1936; 3 items (Box Series I-47)
  - Thomson, Roland D. (Son), 1918-1920; 5 items (Box Series I-47)
  - Thomson Scientific Club, 1891; 2 items (Box Series I-47)
  - Thomson, Stuart (Son), 1915; 1 item (Box Series I-47)
  - Thomson, T. Kennard, 1917-1921; 5 items (Box Series I-47)
  - Thorbe, T. S., 1922; 1 item (Box Series I-47)
  - Throop, F. W., 1892; 1 item (Box Series I-48)
    Cornell University
  - [Thulfall], Richard, 1889; 1 item (Box Series I-48)
    Univ. of Sydney
  - Thurnauer, Ernest, 1901-1913; 6 items (Box Series I-48)
    International Electrical Exhibition
  - Thursday Evening Club, 1920; 1 item (Box Series I-48)
  - Timbie, W. H., 1924-1928; 2 items (Box Series I-48)
    M. I. T. Dept. of Electrical Engineering
  - TIME, 1928; 1 item (Box Series I-48)
  - The Times Engineering Supplement, 1911; 1 item (Box Series I-48)
  - Timm, John A., 1931; 1 item (Box Series I-48)
    Yale Univ. Dept. of Chemistry
  - Titus, Anson Merrill, 1928; 1 item (Box Series I-48)
    Ionic Club
  - Tobey, Harry Willard, n.d.; 1 item (Box Series I-48)
  - Tobey, Horace P., 1894-1915; 5 items (Box Series I-48)
    Tremont Nail Co.
  - Todd, David, 1901-1925; 10 items (Box Series I-48)
  - Todd, James, 1917-1920; 2 items (Box Series I-48)
  - Tokyo Electric Company, n.d.; 1 item (Box Series I-48)
    Postcard from A. Wada
  - Tolman, W. M., 1908; 2 items (Box Series I-48)
  - Toplis, William G., 1893; 2 items (Box Series I-48)
  - Toronto Electric Light Company, 1886-1903; 4 items (Box Series I-48)
    J. J. Wright
  - Towley, Calvert, 1923-1933; 2 items (Box Series I-48)
    See also A. I. E. E. & M. I. T.
  - Townsend, Henry C., 1893-1921; 2 items (Box Series I-48)
  - Townsend, Katharine G., 1913; 1 item (Box Series I-48)
  - Toye, W. H. R., 1891; 1 item (Box Series I-48)
  - Transtrom, H. L., 1907; 2 items (Box Series I-48)
  - Traveller and Clubman, 1929-1930; 5 items (Box Series I-48)
  - Treadwell, James R., 1906; 2 items (Box Series I-48)
  - Trinity College, 1934-1935; 3 items (Box Series I-48)
    R. B. Ogilby
  - Trinity Historical Society, 1891; 1 item (Box Series I-48)
  - Trowbridge, John, 1891-1915; 16 items (Box Series I-48)
    See also: Harvard Univ. Jefferson Physical Lab.
  - Troy, M. O., 1927; 1 item (Box Series I-48)
  - Tucker, F. M. Company, 1902; 1 item (Box Series I-48)
  - Tufts College, 1894-1907; 5 items (Box Series I-48)
  - Tunison's Central Map Establishments, 1902; 1 item (Box Series I-48)
  - Turk, Dr., 1910; 1 item (Box Series I-48)
  - Turner, Frederick J., 1933; 1 item (Box Series I-48)
  - Turner, Ross, 1904; 1 item (Box Series I-48)
  - Turner Tanning Machinery Company, 1928-1929; 4 items (Box Series I-48)
  - Twelfth National Game Conference, 1925; 1 item (Box Series I-48)
  - Udall & Ballou, 1913; 1 item (Box Series I-49)
  - Union College, 1926; 1 item (Box Series I-49)
    C. A. Richmond
  - Union Cycle Manufacturing Company, 1891; 1 item (Box Series I-49)
  - Union Phosphate Company, 1896; 1 item (Box Series I-49)
  - United Business Service, 1932; 2 items (Box Series I-49)
    Paul Talbot
  - United Concrete Machinery Company, 1905; 1 item (Box Series I-49)
  - United Electric Light Company, 1924; 2 items (Box Series I-49)
    Robert W. Day
  - United Electric Light and Power Company, 1 item (Box Series I-49)
  - United Engineering Society, 1907-1917; 5 items (Box Series I-49)
  - United Fruit Company, 1927; 1 item (Box Series I-49)
  - United Metals Selling Company, 1916; 1 item (Box Series I-49)
  - United Mining Company, 1906; 1 item (Box Series I-49)
  - United Mining and Development Company, 1903; 2 items (Box Series I-49)
  - United Scientific Company, 1913; 3 items (Box Series I-49)
  - United States. Army Ordinance Association, 1925; 1 item (Box Series I-49)
  - United States. Capitol. Architect"s Office, 1893; 2 items (Box Series I-49)
    W. E. Woods
  - United States. Civil Service Commission, 1917-1918; 4 items (Box Series I-49)
  - United States: Department of Agriculture, 1892-1923; 7 items (Box Series I-49)
    Weather Bureau, Bureau of Chemistry and Bureau of Plant Industry
  - United States. Department of Commerce, 1925; 3 items (Box Series I-49)
    Bureau of Mines
  - United States. Department of Commerce, 1918-1923; 6 items (Box Series I-49)
  - United States. Department of Commerce, 1922-1932; 3 items (Box Series I-49)
    Office of the Secretary
  - United States. Department of Commerce and Labor, 1891-1905; 4 items (Box Series I-49)
    Bureau of the Census
  - United States. Department of Commerce and Labor, 1903-1913; 20 items (Box Series I-49)
  - United States. Department of Commerce and Labor, 1903-1908; 5 items (Box Series I-49)
  - United States. Department of the Interior, 1899-1918; 7 items (Box Series I-49)
  - United States. Department of Justice, 1891; 1 item (Box Series I-49)
  - United States. Department of the Navy, 1917; 1 item (Box Series I-49)
    Bureau of Construction and Repair
  - United States. Department of the Navy, 1915; 2 items (Box Series I-49)
    Bureau of Steam Engineering
  - United States. Department of the Navy, 1894-1924; 3 items (Box Series I-49)
    Bureau of Yards & Docks
  - United States. Department of the Navy, 1916-1917; 32 items (Box Series I-49)
    Naval Consulting Board
  - United States. Department of the Navy, 1918-1924; 3 items (Box Series I-49)
  - United States. Department of State, 1893-1932; 8 items (Box Series I-49)
    Coast & Geodetic Survey, Passport Bureau, Secretary of State
  - United States. Department of the Treasury, 1900-1919; 14 items (Box Series I-49)
  - United States. Electrical Commission, 1884; 1 item (Box Series I-49)
  - United States. House of Representatives, 1892-1930; 2 items (Box Series I-49)
  - United States. House of Representatives, 1902; 6 items (Box Series I-49)
    Committee on Coinage, Weights and Measures
  - United States. Patent Office, 1912-1929; 3 items (Box Series I-49)
  - United States. Post Office, 1891-1919; 8 items (Box Series I-49)
  - United States. Senate, 1908-1933; 3 items (Box Series I-49)
  - United States. War Department, 1917-1922; 2 items (Box Series I-49)
  - United States Diesel Engineering School, 1933; 1 item (Box Series I-49)
  - United States Electric Lighting Company, 1895; 2 items (Box Series I-49)
  - United States Fuel Administration, 1918; 1 item (Box Series I-49)
    Oil Division
  - United States History Association, 1927; 1 item (Box Series I-49)
  - United States Smelting, Refining and Mining, 1914-1919; 7 items (Box Series I-49)
  - Universal Electrical Directory, 1912; 1 item (Box Series I-49)
    H. Alabaster Gatehouse & Co.
  - Universal Exposition, St. Louis 1904, 1903-1904; 3 items (Box Series I-49)
    International Congresses
  - University of California, 1905-1924; 5 items (Box Series I-49)
    Lick Observatory & Misc.
  - University of Chicago & Institute of American Meat Packers, 1925; 1 item (Box Series I-49)
  - University of Cincinnati. Department of Physics, 1930; 1 item (Box Series I-49)
    D. A. Wells
  - University of Illinois, 1906-1924; 5 items (Box Series I-49)
  - University of London, University College, 1926; 1 item (Box Series I-49)
  - University Magazine Company, 1892; 1 item (Box Series I-49)
  - University Magazine Company, 1892; 1 item (Box Series I-49)
    Spence O. Ovington
  - University of Manchester, 1924; 4 items (Box Series I-49)
    Sir Henry A. Miers
  - University of Michigan. Engineering Dept., 1891; 2 items (Box Series I-49)
    Frank C. Wagner
  - University of Missouri. School of Engineering, 1904; 2 items (Box Series I-49)
    H. B. Shaw
  - University of Nebraska. Department of Electrical and Steam Engineering, 1897; 3 items (Box Series I-49)
    R. B. Owens
  - University of New Hampshire, 1932; 1 item (Box Series I-49)
    Stuart Dunn
  - University of Pennsylvania, 1910-1926; 9 items (Box Series I-49)
    Sigma Xi, Moore School of Elec. Engineering
  - University Press, 1894; 1 item (Box Series I-49)
    John Wilson
  - University of Texas, 1894; 1 item (Box Series I-49)
    Alexander MacFarlane
  - University of Wisconsin. College of Mechanics & Engineers, 1904-1919; 3 items (Box Series I-49)
  - UNKNOWN CORRESPONDENTS, 1887-1933; 26 items (Box Series I-50)
  - Upton, A. A., 1910; 1 item (Box Series I-50)
    Equitable Club of Change
  - Van Anda, C. V., 1932; 2 items (Box Series I-50)
  - Van Depoele, Mrs. C. J., 1894; 2 items (Box Series I-50)
  - Vanderbilt Hotel, 1914-1931; 2 items (Box Series I-50)
    Walter H. Marshall
  - Van Nostrand, D. Company, 1909; 1 item (Box Series I-50)
  - Van Slyck Publishing Company, 1910; 1 item (Box Series I-50)
  - Vauclain, Samuel M., 1925; 2 items (Box Series I-50)
    Baldwin Locomotive Works
  - Vaughn, George, 1933; 1 item (Box Series I-50)
  - Veeder, Curtis H., 1905-1932; 15 items (Box Series I-50)
    Veeder Manufacturing Co.
  - Venable, William Mayo, 1922-1928; 5 items (Box Series I-50)
  - Vesper, A. F., 1929; 1 item (Box Series I-50)
  - Veterans of Foreign Wars, 1931; 1 item (Box Series I-50)
  - Vezey, E. E., 1929; 1 item (Box Series I-50)
    Agricultural and Mech. College of Texas.
  - Victor X-Ray Corporation, 1925; 1 item (Box Series I-50)
    C. Darnell
  - Vidal & Fils, J. L. O., 1892; 1 item (Box Series I-50)
  - Viets, Mr., 1903; 1 item (Box Series I-50)
  - Violli, J., 1897; 1 item (Box Series I-50)
  - Voltampere, Gray, n.d.; 2 items (Box Series I-50)
  - Walker, F. A., 1891; 1 item (Box Series I-50)
  - Von Miller, Oskar, 1912-1913; 12 items (Box Series I-50)
    See also: Deutsches Museum
  - Wagoner, C. D., 1933-1944; 3 items (Box Series I-50)
  - Wakefield, W. O., 1899; 2 items (Box Series I-50)
  - Waldron, Frederick A., 1907; 1 item (Box Series I-50)
  - Walker, Albert, 1892; 1 item (Box Series I-50)
  - Walker, John Brisben, 1904-1930; 6 items (Box Series I-50)
  - Walker, Miles, 1925-1928; 2 items (Box Series I-50)
    Victoria University of Manchester
  - Wall Street Journal, 1931-1933; 2 items (Box Series I-50)
  - Wallace, Charles F., 1892; 1 item (Box Series I-50)
  - Wallace, William, 1932; 1 item (Box Series I-50)
  - Walmsley, R. Mullineux, 1903-1910; 7 items (Box Series I-50)
    Northampton Polytechnic Institute
  - Wallis-Jones, Reginald I., 1923; 1 item (Box Series I-50)
    Wallis-Jones & Dent
  - Wallman, H. F., 1916; 3 items (Box Series I-50)
  - Waltham Electric Clock Company, 1891; 1 item (Box Series I-50)
    E. M. Currie
  - Waltham Manufacturing Company, 1897; 1 item (Box Series I-50)
    Nathan Clifford
  - Walworth, Mr., 1900; 1 item (Box Series I-50)
  - Ward, Curtis T., 1927; 1 item (Box Series I-50)
  - Ward, Herbert D., 1900; 5 items (Box Series I-50)
  - Wardell, Phineas, 1893; 1 item (Box Series I-50)
    Lawrence, Wilde & Co.
  - Wardnell, E. M., 1932; 1 item (Box Series I-50)
  - Waring, Duncan, 1892; 1 item (Box Series I-50)
  - Warner Instrument Company, 1903-1906; 8 items (Box Series I-50)
    D. W. Dunn
  - Warner, Lucien, 1915; 1 item (Box Series I-50)
    YMCA- International Committee
  - Warner and Swasey, 1899-1930; 7 items (Box Series I-50)
  - Warren Debating Society, 1900; 1 item (Box Series I-50)
    Frank B. Portland
  - Warren, Garfield, Whiteside & Lamson, 1918; 1 item (Box Series I-50)
  - Warriner, S. D., 1914; 2 items (Box Series I-50)
    Alaska Copper Co.
  - Washington Academy of Sciences, 1924; 1 item (Box Series I-50)
  - Waterman, F. N., 1898-1903; 6 items (Box Series I-50)
    Westinghouse Elec. & Manufacturing Co.
  - Watson, Arthur E., 1930; 1 item (Box Series I-50)
    Brown Univ. Photo of Dynamo
  - Watson, C. A., 1899; 1 item (Box Series I-50)
  - Watson, William, 1900; 1 item (Box Series I-50)
  - Wave Power Motor Company, 1899; 1 item (Box Series I-50)
    William Newell, Sr.
  - Weart, A. R., 1912; 2 items (Box Series I-51)
  - Weaver, Roger M., 1895; 2 items (Box Series I-51)
  - Weaver, W. D., 1900-1916; 13 items (Box Series I-51)
    See also: U.S. House of Reps. & Elec. World
  - Webber(Wilbur), Henry, 1906; 2 items (Box Series I-51)
  - Webster, Arthur G., 1893-1921; 17 items (Box Series I-51)
    Clark Univ. Dept. of Physics
  - Webster. Edwin S., 1907-1935; 5 items (Box Series I-51)
  - Webster, F. W., 1897; 2 items (Box Series I-51)
  - Weddleton, William, 1916; 1 item (Box Series I-51)
  - Weed, D. W., 1929; 1 item (Box Series I-51)
  - Weeks, Edwin R., 1892-1930; 14 items (Box Series I-51)
  - Welby, C. Montgomery, 1902; 1 item (Box Series I-51)
    International Peace Exhibition 1904
  - Welch, John C., 1899; 4 items (Box Series I-51)
  - Wellman, H., 1901; 1 item (Box Series I-51)
    Camden Inter-State Ry.
  - Wellman, H., 1933; 1 item (Box Series I-51)
    Enterprise Electric Co.
  - Wells, Mr. & Mrs. Albert, n.d.; 1 item (Box Series I-51)
  - Wells, James H., 1898; 2 items (Box Series I-51)
  - Wells, Robert, 1930; 1 item (Box Series I-51)
  - Welsh, Charles, 1906; 2 items (Box Series I-51)
  - Welsh, Herbert, 1903; 1 item (Box Series I-51)
  - Wentworth, Arioch, 1896; 1 item (Box Series I-51)
  - Werner Company, 1896; 5 items (Box Series I-51)
  - West End Street Railway Company, 1895; 2 items (Box Series I-51)
  - West, Goldsmith Bernard, 1891; 1 item (Box Series I-51)
    Jacksonville Mining and Manufacturing Co.
  - West, Robert, 1933; 1 item (Box Series I-51)
  - West, Theodore B., 1891; 1 item (Box Series I-51)
  - Westbury, Harry, 1901-1905; 14 items (Box Series I-51)
  - Western Association of Electrical Inspectors, 1925; 3 items (Box Series I-51)
    William S. Boyd
  - Western Electric Company, 1898-1931; 4 items (Box Series I-51)
  - Western Electrician, 1892-1907; 29 items (Box Series I-51)
  - Western Reserve University, 1903; 3 items (Box Series I-51)
  - Western Society of Engineers, 1904-1928; 2 items (Box Series I-51)
  - Western Union Telegraph Company, 1901; 1 item (Box Series I-51)
  - Westinghouse Electric Company, 1921; 1 item (Box Series I-51)
  - Westinghouse, George Memorial Association, 1930; 1 item (Box Series I-51)
  - Westman, A. E. R., 1928; 1 item (Box Series I-51)
  - Weston Dotson & Company, Inc., 1926; 1 item (Box Series I-51)
    C. E. Mengel
  - Weston, Edward, 1892-1926; 4 items (Box Series I-51)
    Weston Electrical Instrument Co.
  - Westover, M. F., 1923-1931; 3 items (Box Series I-51)
  - Wetherill, Henry Emerson, 1930; 1 item (Box Series I-51)
  - Wetzler, Joseph, 1891-1899; 6 items (Box Series I-51)
    See also: Electrical Engineer
  - Wharton, C. J., 1931; 1 item (Box Series I-51)
  - Wharton, Mrs. C. J. & Sybil, 1935-1936; 3 items (Box Series I-51)
  - Wheeler, H. W., 1892; 1 item (Box Series I-51)
  - White Company, 1908; 3 items (Box Series I-51)
    L. C. Franz
  - White, Mrs. Harriet A., 1933; 1 item (Box Series I-51)
  - White, James T. & Company, 1891-1926; 9 items (Box Series I-51)
  - White, J. G., 1911; 2 items (Box Series I-51)
  - White Star Line, 1905; 3 items (Box Series I-51)
  - White, William F., 1904; 2 items (Box Series I-51)
    North American Company
  - Whitehead, John B., 1925; 2 items (Box Series I-51)
  - Whitfield, William L., 1899; 2 items (Box Series I-51)
  - Whiting Club, 1918-1928; 2 items (Box Series I-51)
  - Whiting, Sarah F., 1901; 1 item (Box Series I-51)
    Wellesley College. Physical Laboratory
  - Whitman, William, 1902; 5 items (Box Series I-51)
  - Whitney, D., 1891; 1 item (Box Series I-51)
  - Whitney, John H., 1901; 2 items (Box Series I-51)
  - Whitney, Willis R., 1902-1935; 24 items (Box Series I-51)
  - Whittaker & Company, 1899; 1 item (Box Series I-51)
  - Wiard, A. L., 1895; 1 item (Box Series I-51)
  - Wiemann, W. P., 1895; 2 items (Box Series I-51)
  - Wigglesworth, George, 1903-1906; 3 items (Box Series I-51)
  - Wightman, Merle J., 1891-1933; 21 items (Box Series I-51)
  - Wiley, Harvey W., 1928; 3 items (Box Series I-52)
  - Wiley, John & Sons, 1893-1899; 2 items (Box Series I-52)
  - Wilkeby, George, n.d.; 1 item (Box Series I-52)
  - Willcomb, Annie E., 1933; 2 items (Box Series I-52)
  - Wille, H. V., 1891-1892; 4 items (Box Series I-52)
    Student at Cornell University
  - Williams, Arthur, 1917-1926; 3 items (Box Series I-52)
  - Williams, Emile F., 1915; 1 item (Box Series I-52)
  - Williams, Francis H., 1896-1912; 16 items (Box Series I-52)
  - Williams Manufacturing Company, n.d.; 1 item (Box Series I-52)
  - Williams, Nelson J., 1895; 2 items (Box Series I-52)
  - Williams, Percy, 1891; 1 item (Box Series I-52)
    Colorado School of Mines student
  - Williams, W. N., 1899; 2 items (Box Series I-52)
  - Willis, H., 1895; 1 item (Box Series I-52)
  - Willson, Theodore B., 1908; 1 item (Box Series I-52)
  - Wilson, E. B., 1917-1930; 2 items (Box Series I-52)
    See also: M. I. T.
  - Wilson, Fred, 1924; 1 item (Box Series I-52)
  - Wilson, J. S., 1931; 2 items (Box Series I-52)
  - Wilson, Louis N., 1895; 2 items (Box Series I-52)
  - Wilson Maculen Company, 1907; 1 item (Box Series I-52)
  - Wilson, R. D. & Company, 1894; 4 items (Box Series I-52)
  - Wilson, R. Wayne Company, 1895; 2 items (Box Series I-52)
  - Windsor Collar and Cuff Company, 1899; 1 item (Box Series I-52)
  - Windsor, Mr., 1895; 1 item (Box Series I-52)
    See original @ W. E. Ayrton
  - Winifrede Coal Company, 1896; 3 items (Box Series I-52)
  - Wirt, Paul E. Fountain Pen, 1897-1903; 3 items (Box Series I-52)